

# Nigel Mulholland

#### TEST AUTOMATION SPECIALIST

Seasoned QA professional with 5+ years of industry experience. Known for clear communication, multitasking prowess, and keen attention to detail with knowledge across diverse projects and domains. Enthusiastic about test automation and certified in ISTOB-CTFL.

#### **CONTACT**

 $\bigvee$ 

nigeldave19@gmail.com



+94 71 612 6546



linkedin/nigel-mulholland



github/youvegotnigel



Negombo, Sri Lanka

#### **EDUCATION**

2016 - 2019

# University of Sri Jayewardenepura

Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.)

## **SKILLS | EXTRAS**



#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Associate Lead - Quality Engineering**

VitalHub Innovations Lab, 05/2023 - Present

- Lead the test automation team, mentor new team members, and conduct KT sessions.
- Review test automation reports and highlight problem areas.
- Technologies used: Cypress, TypeScript, Azure DevOps

#### **Senior Quality Assurance Engineer**

VitalHub Innovations Lab, 03/2021 - 04/2023

- Web, API, and Mobile Automation.
- Performance testing.
- Develop BDD test automation framework with Cypress.
- Technologies used: Katalon Studio, Cucumber, JMeter, SauceLabs, GIT, Sourcetree, Bitbucket

### **Software Quality Assurance Engineer**

Zilingo, 01/2020 - 02/2021

- Test planning, test strategy creation.
- API testing, mobile testing, and automation.
- Developed functional UI Test Automation Frameworks for web-based applications.
- Technologies used: Postman, Selenium, Java, Appium

## **Associate Quality Assurance Engineer**

nCinga Innovations, 01/2019 - 12/2019

- Manual testing on web and mobile-based applications.
- Test case writing and documentation.
- Supported gaining ROI in the regression
- Technologies used: Google Docs, JIRA, Jenkins, Protractor, JavaScript